biotherm.com 2016-11-22

# Privacy Policy

### **Purpose**

Biotherm, a division of L'Oreal Canada, Inc., has adopted this Privacy Statement in order to inform you of its policies with respect to information collected from this website. Your use of this website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Statement and your consent to the practices it describes.

### **Personally Identifiable Information**

Personally Identifiable Information is any information that concerns you individually and would permit someone to contact you, for example, your name, address, telephone/fax number, social security number, email address or any information you submitted to Biotherm.com that identifies you individually.

Biotherm.com will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it. Therefore, if you do not want Biotherm.com to obtain any personally identifiable information about you, do not submit it.

You can visit and browse the Biotherm website without revealing personally identifiable information about yourself. You may also choose to disclose personally identifiable information about yourself, which may be maintained as described below.

Biotherm.com may collect personally identifiable information about you when you register with one of our divisions or brands, for example to enter our contests, join our mailing lists or become our privileged customer, you may be asked for personal information such as, but not restricted to, your contact information (name, telephone numbers, e-mail address, mailing address), date of birth, product and/or cosmetic concerns, which brands and products you use, security information (user name and password).

You may also be asked additional marketing-related questions by completing questionnaires, surveys and profile data to help us better understand your needs and those of potential customers. You may also be requested to give your delivery and billing address, credit card number and expiration date when you place an order.

### **Transactions and Activity**

If you become a registered user or if you conduct transactions through the Biotherm website, Biotherm.com collects information about the transactions you engage in while on the website and your other activity on the site. This information may include, without limitation, areas of the website that you visit, transaction type, content that you view, download or submit, transaction amount, payment, shipping and billing information as well as the nature, quantity and price of the goods or services you exchange and the individuals or entities with whom you communicate or transact business.

### **Information Use**

Biotherm.com may use the personally identifiable information collected through its website primarily for such purposes as:

  * Helping to establish and verify the identity of users;
  * Opening, maintaining, administering and servicing users' accounts or memberships;
  * Processing, servicing or enforcing transactions and sending related communications;
  * Providing services and support to users;
  * Improving the website, including tailoring it to users' preferences;
  * Providing users with product or service updates, promotional notices and offers, and other information about Biotherm and its affiliates;
  * Responding to your questions inquiries, comments and instructions;
  * Maintaining the security and integrity of its systems.

Biotherm.com uses the anonymous browsing information collected automatically by its servers primarily to help it administer and improve its website. Biotherm.com may also use aggregated anonymous information to provide information about its website to advertisers, potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities. Again, this information is not personally identifiable.

### **Children's Privacy**

This website is directed toward and designed for use by persons aged 13 or older. Biotherm.com will not approve applications of, or establish or maintain accounts or memberships for, any child whom Biotherm.com knows to be under the age of 13. Biotherm.com does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If Biotherm.com nevertheless discovers that it has received personally identifiable information from an individual who indicates that he or she is, or whom Biotherm otherwise has reason to believe is, under the age of 13, Biotherm.com will delete such information from its systems. Additionally, a child's parent or legal guardian may request that the child's information be corrected or deleted from Biotherm.com's files by using our Contact Us Form.

External Links

The Biotherm website may contain links to other websites, including those of advertisers or third party content providers who offer downloads on Biotherm.com. Please be aware that Biotherm is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites. Websites that are accessible by hyperlinks from the Biotherm website may use cookies. Biotherm encourages you to read the privacy statements provided by other websites before you provide personally identifiable information to them.

### **Choice/Opt-Out**

In order to provide service to you, Biotherm.com will send you communications related to your transactions, security or the administration of its website. From time to time, Biotherm.com and its affiliates brands may also wish to send you other messages or updates about Biotherm.com, its affiliates, or their promotions and other activities. If you do not wish to receive non-transaction/security related communications from Biotherm.com and its affiliates, please send an email containing your request to customer service.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Biotherm.com reserves the right to modify or supplement this policy at any time. If a material change to the terms of this policy is made, Biotherm.com will post a notice on its homepage and a link to the new policy.

### **Automatic Collection of Anonymous Information**

When you visit the Biotherm website, like when you visit most other websites, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically logged, which may include information about the type of browser you use, the server name and IP address through which you access the internet (such as "aol.com" or "earthlink.net"), the date and time you access the site, the pages you access while at the Biotherm website, and the internet address of the website, if any, from which you linked directly to the Biotherm site. This information is not personally identifiable.

### **Registration Forms**

If you are offered the opportunity to enter a promotion, to become a registered user of the Biotherm website, or to opt-in to receive Biotherm information through another site, you must apply by filling out the registration form on the site. This form requires certain personally identifiable information that may include, without limitation, your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, areas of interest, product usage, and/or a unique individual password. You may also choose to communicate with Biotherm.com through email, via our website, by telephone, in writing, or though other means. We collect the information in these communications, and such information may be personally identifiable.

### **Disclosure of Information**

Biotherm.com does not provide personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their use in marketing directly to you. Biotherm may use unaffiliated companies to help it maintain and operate its website or for other reasons related to the operation of its business, and those companies may receive your personally identifiable information for that purpose. Biotherm may also disclose personally identifiable information about you in connection with legal requirements, such as in response to an authorized subpoena, governmental request or investigation, or as otherwise permitted by law. Finally, as Biotherm business develops, it may sell or buy corporate assets, and in such transactions customer information may be one of the transferred business assets. If Biotherm, its internet businesses, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired, customer information may be one of the assets transferred.

### **"Cookies" and Advertisers**

The Biotherm website's server, or the servers of companies that are used to operate this site, may place a "cookie" on your computer in order to allow you to use the website and to personalize your experience.

A "cookie" is a small piece of data that can be sent by a web server to your computer, which then may be stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow Biotherm.com to recognize your computer while you are on its website and help customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you. Cookies are also useful in allowing more efficient log-in for users, tracking transaction histories and preserving information between sessions. The information collected from cookies may also be used to improve the functionality of the website.

The advertisers and/or other content providers that may appear on this website may also use cookies that are not sent by the Biotherm website. Such ads or content may contain cookies that help track and target the interests of users of this website in order to present "personalized" advertisements or other messages that the user might find interesting. Biotherm is not responsible for any such cookies.

Most web browser applications (such as Microsoft Internet Explorer and Firefox) have features that can notify you when you receive a cookie or prevent cookies from being sent. If you disable cookies, however, you may not be able to use certain personalized functions of this website.

### **Security**

Biotherm.com maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help guard personally identifiable information. If transactions are offered on the site, transaction information is transmitted to and from Biotherm.com in encrypted form using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect such information from interception. Biotherm.com restricts authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide products or services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information. Please be aware, however, that any email or other transmission you send through the internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception.

### **Data Quality/Access**

Biotherm.com allows you to change, update, or delete the information you may provide in your optional registration form. If you would like to change, update, or delete your personal information, please send an email containing your request to customer service.
